Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Personal Files, 1824-present UA.Personal.Files
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- S
  - Stouthamer-Loeber, Magda
  - Stover, Nello
  - Stowe, Robert
  - Stoy, Walt A.
  - Strada, Gino
  - Stranahan, Patricia
  - Strathern, Andrew J.
  - Straub, Darel *
  - Straub, William H.
  - Strauss, Marilyn
  - Strauss, Mark S.
  - Strauss, Susan *
  - Streeter, Sybil
  - Stremecki, Joseph
  - Stremple, John F. *
  - Strick, Ellis
  - Strick, Peter L.
  - Stricker, Edward
  - Strickland, Douglas Jerry
  - Strickland, William E.
  - Stricklin, William
  - Striegel, Adam
  - Striker, Edward M. (Professor)
  - Stringfield, James K.
  - Stripp, Barry
  - Strom, Stephen
  - Strong, Justin
  - Strong, Tracy B.
  - Strong, W. W.
  - Strothers, Stewart Washington *
  - Strothman, Randy
  - Stryker, Roy *
  - Stryker, Walter H.
  - Strzempka, Paul
  - Stuart, Edward B. *
  - Stuckart, Michael
  - Stuckless, E. Ross
  - Studen-Pavlovich, Deborah
  - Studenski, Stephanie
  - Stueart, Robert
  - Stunkard, Charles M.
  - Sturdivant, Linda
  - Sturdivant, Michael L.
  - Sturk, Roland
  - Sturzenhsfecker, Gabriele
  - Stutzman, Millo J.
  - Stvczek, Andrzej
  - Styan, John L. *
  - Su, Louise T.
  - Subotnick, Morton *
  - Suchman, Edward A.
  - Suda, Zdenek L.
  - Sudhakar, Reddy P. *
  - Sued, Alan
  - Sukits, Jay
  - Sulkowski, Eugene L.
  - Sullivan, David C.
  - Sullivan, Lester *
  - Sullivan, Peggy
  - Sullivan, Robert M.
  - Sulpher, Natalie
  - Sumarlin, Johannes
  - Summers, David
  - Sundaralingam, Muttaiya
  - Sunseri, Sal
  - Supowitz, Paul
  - Suscop, Ruth
  - Susko, Jeanne
  - Susser, Marray "Buzz"
  - Sussman, Maurice
  - Sussman, Raquel
  - Sussna, Edward *
  - Sustar, J. J. (Colonel) *
  - Sutherland, Cynthia
  - Sutherland, James Runcieman (Dr.)
  - Sutherland, John "Jock" (oversize) *
  - Sutherland, Robert (Dr.)
  - Sutila, Jan
  - Sutin, Steward
  - Sutton, George Miksch
  - Sutton-Tyrrell, Kim
  - Suzuki, David T.
  - Suzuki, Jon Byron
  - Svejnar, Jan
  - Swan, Oscar
  - Swank, Luke
  - Swanson, Dennis P.
  - Swanson, Dianne
  - Swanson, John A.
  - Swanson, William F.
  - Swarts, Donald *
  - Swartwout, Joseph (Dr.)
  - Swartzbaugh, William L. *
  - Swartzel, Karl Dale
  - Swayze, Daniel R.
  - Sweadner, Walter R.
  - Sweeley, Charles (Dr.)
  - Sweeney, John
  - Sweeney, Maureen M.
  - Sweeney, Megan
  - Sweet, Richard
  - Sweet, Robert
  - Swenson, Cole
  - Swietolslawski, Wojciech
  - Swift, Charles
  - Swift, Elisha P.
  - Swigert, Valerie
  - Swilley, Graylyn
  - Swink, Brad
  - Swinscoe, Thomas
  - Swoboda, Merrily K.
  - Swope, Harper E.
  - Swope, W. Wylie
  - Swort, Arlowayne
  - Sykora, Jan L.
  - Sylvestre, Anthony
  - Syphan, Janet
  - Syme, Sir Ronald
  - Syverson, Chad
  - Sze, Tsung Wei *
  - Szeri, Andras
  - Szeto, Isabel
  - Szymanowski, Waclaw
- T
  - Tabatabai, Mahmood *
  - Tabb, Tia
  - Taber, George
  - Taber, Joseph J. *
  - Tacey, H. S.
  - Tacey, William S. (oversize) *
  - Tadjziechy, Mahnaz *
  - Tadokoro, Masayuki
  - Tafel, James B.
  - Taft, Chris
  - Taft. Lori
  - Taintor, Charles Wilson *
  - Tait, Edward T.
  - Tait, Lilia G.
  - Takimoto, Koichi
  - Talbott, Evelyn
  - Talese, Gay
  - Tallarico, Michelle D.
  - Talsma, Valerie
  - Tambellini, Bruno
  - Tan Sri Ong Yoke Lin *
  - Tang, Man-Chung
  - Tang, Wen Fang
  - Tannacito, Dan
  - Tannehill, Wilkins *
  - Tansky, Burton Marvin
  - Tantisira, Boonrak *
  - Tarbell, Sally
  - Tarquinio, Ron
  - Tartak, Marvin *
  - Tartaron, Francis X. *
  - Tarter, Ralph
  - Taube, Myron *
  - Tauber, Michael
  - Tauberg, Stuart
  - Taulbee, Orrin E. *
  - Taylor, Arlene
  - Taylor, Carl
  - Taylor, Carole (Dr.)
  - Taylor, David
  - Taylor, James F.
  - Taylor, James S. *
  - Taylor, Jerome
  - Taylor, John
  - Taylor, Jo'ie
  - Taylor, Kellii
  - Taylor, Marcus
  - Taylor, Mary Florence *
  - Taylor, Michelle Scott
  - Taylor, Paul M.
  - Taylor, Rebecca Frances Drew
  - Taylor, Robert W.
  - Taylor, Roger
  - Taylor, Ruth
  - Taylor, Samuel A.
  - Taylor, Vince
  - Tchou, Patrick
  - Teagarden, Florence M. *
  - Teal, Elizabeth
  - Teaster, Richard
  - Teats, Jean E.
  - Teegarden, Erin
  - Teich, Alan
  - Telep, Sandra
  - Teller, Edward
  - Temkin, Larry
  - Templeton, Bryce
  - Tenicela, Ruben
  - Teplitz, Esther F.
  - Tepper, David A.
  - Tesh, Kendall S. *
  - Tesla, Nikola
  - Tharp, Michael *
  - Thase, Michael
  - Thaw, Alexander Blair
  - Thaw, Benjamin, Sr. *
  - Thaw, William *
  - Thayer, Clarence
  - Thayer, Fredrick (oversize)
  - Theisen, Carrie Ann
  - Themudo, Nuno
  - Thielmann, Greg
  - Thiels, Edda
  - Thiesen, Marcia
  - Thiessen, Gilbert
  - Thoft, Richard A.
  - Thomas, Arthur B.
  - Thomas, Bernard G. H.
  - Thomas, Bryan
  - Thomas, Christopher
  - Thomas, Clarke M.
  - Thomas, Elinore S.
  - Thomas, George (Dr.)
  - Thomas, Henry William
  - Thomas, Herb *
  - Thomas, J. W.
  - Thomas, Janet D.
  - Thomas, Jim
  - Thomas, Joan *
  - Thomas, Julie *
  - Thomas, Lacey
  - Thomas, Mary Ann
  - Thomas, Mary P.
  - Thomas, Maurice J. *
  - Thomas, Stephen (Dr.)
  - Thomas, William B.
  - Thomason, Richard
  - Thomason, Sarah
  - Thompson, A. H. (Dr.)
  - Thompson, Alexander M. *
  - Thompson, Carolyn
  - Thompson, Charles
  - Thompson, Donovan J. (Dr.)
  - Thompson, Dorothy K. G. *
  - Thompson, Douglass
  - Thompson, Elmer Palmer "E. P."
  - Thompson, George J.
  - Thompson, J. L. *
  - Thompson, Jane
  - Thompson, James D. *
  - Thompson, John H.
  - Thompson, John R.
  - Thompson, Joseph H.
  - Thompson, Julia
  - Thompson, Karim
  - Thompson, Kay F.
  - Thompson, Kenneth
  - Thompson, Mary Deman (SEE Deman, Mary)
  - Thompson, Mark *
  - Thompson, Paul D.
  - Thompson, Phillip
  - Thompson, Richard A.
  - Thompson, Rochelle
  - Thompson, Timothy S.
  - Thompson, Warren
  - Thomson, Angus
  - Thonard, John C.
  - Thorley, Joseph Palin
  - Thorn, Richard S.
  - Thornburgh, Richard *
  - Thornton, James
  - Thorp, Sharon
  - Thorpe, Francis N.
  - Thorpe, Harvey E.
  - Thorpe, Melvin A.
  - Thralls, Zoe A. *
  - Thrayer, Lynn W. (oversize) *
  - Throft, Richard A.
  - Tibby, Jack
  - Tiedemann, Beth
  - Tierney, Jack
  - Tierney, John W. (Dr.) *
  - Tierney, Patrick
  - Tilghman, William
  - Tillotson, E. Ward
  - Tilmans, Anthony L.
  - Timm, Neil
  - Timmins, Robert
  - Tinker, C. Harold (Rev.)
  - Tinsley, William C. (Colonel) *
  - Tintner, Gerhard
  - Tipper, David W.
  - Tippetts, Charles S. *
  - Tipton, Emily
  - Tisberman, Samuel
  - Tita, William T.
  - Titchworth, Roy L.
  - Tittrick, Emie
  - Titus, James Rodger
  - Tkach, Walter
  - Tobias, Barbara
  - Tobias, Richard C. *
  - Tobler, Keeley
  - Tobon, Hector
  - Todd, Emerson Howard
  - Todd, Marjorie
  - Todd, Tennile
  - Todd, William T.
  - Todhunter, John
  - Todo, Satoru
  - Tofovic, Steven
  - Toker, Franklin
  - Toko, Gad William
  - Tollerud, David (Dr.)
  - Tolley, William P.
  - Tolliver, Charles
  - Tomalis, Matt
  - Tomassetti, Dennis H.
  - Tomazich, Jamie
  - Tomer, Christinger *
  - Tomko, Joe
  - Tompkins, Connie
  - Tomsho, Doris M.
  - Toncic, Ivan
  - Toner, Vee
  - Toney, Monique
  - Tong, Hollington K.
  - Tong, Tae Kwon
  - Tong, Winton
  - Tonsor, Stephen
  - Toomey, Regis (oversize)
  - Toplak, Wendy
  - Tornquist, Gerhard
  - Torok, Frank
  - Torres, Nestor
  - Tortella, Gabriel
  - Tosatta, Franis L. "Frank"
  - Tosh, Kathy P.
  - Totten, David
  - Totten, Robert S. (Dr.)
  - Totten, William J. *
  - Toulmin, George B.
  - Townsend, David
  - Townsend, John R.
  - Traficant, James
  - Trager, Jonathan
  - Trahan, Elizabeth *
  - Trakselis, Michael
  - Tranter, William D.
  - Traunsteiner, Albert
  - Trauth, Jeannette
  - Trautman, George (Mrs.) *
  - Travis, Georgia *
  - Travis, Ralph
  - Trebec, Marie M. *
  - Tredennick, Donald C.
  - Trees, Joseph C. (oversize)
  - Trellis, Emil, MD
  - Tremblay, Wilfred
  - Trenary, Michael
  - Tretheway, Natasha
  - Treu, Siegfried *
  - Treuting, Waldo L.
  - Trieu, Nguyen Tan
  - Triggs, Anita
  - Trilli, Harvey J. *
  - Trilli, Lauren E.
  - Trimble, David
  - Trinity, John P.
  - Tritch, Stephen R.
  - Tritschler, Donald
  - Tronzo, Louis
  - Trout, Harry E. *
  - Troutman, Chevon
  - Troxel, Wendy
  - Troy, Rick
  - Trucano, Peter
  - Trucco, Massimo
  - Trump, Donald L.
  - Truschel, Patricia Ann
  - Truxel, Wendy
  - Tryon, Clarence A. *
  - Tsang, (Dr.)
  - Tsao, Sabrina
  - Tsi-Lin, Mei
  - Tsuda, Eiichi
  - Tsui, Fu-Chiang
  - Tsui, Lap-Chee
  - Tsuji, Fred
  - Tuchi, Ben Joseph
  - Tucker, William
  - Tuden, Arthur *
  - Tuerke, Helmut
  - Tuitt, Nelson L.
  - Tullick, William C. *
  - Tumazos, Charles T.
  - Tung, C. C.
  - Turk, Dennis C.
  - Turkes, W. R. *
  - Turman, John
  - Turnball, Jessie J. *
  - Turner, H. Woodruff
  - Turner, Harry
  - Turner, J. Harvard
  - Turner, Martha
  - Turner, Ralph
  - Turner, Rollo
  - Turner, Sekai
  - Turnshek, David
  - Tweedale, Martin M.
  - Twiss, Thomas
  - Tyler, Ralph W.
  - Tymitz, John
  - Tyner, James
  - Tyrell, Kim S.
  - Tyson, Francis D. (oversize) *
  - Tyson, Gretchen
  - Tyson, Stephen J.
  - Tzakis, Andreas *
- U
  - Udin, Sala
  - Ulery, Irene
  - Ulin, Donald
  - Ullery, Gina
  - Ullman, Berthold L.
  - Ulmer, Russell
  - Ulrich, John H.
  - Ulsh, Marie
  - Ulsh, Richard
  - Unangst, Mike
  - Underwood, James M. *
  - Ungar, Mary
  - Urbach, Andrew H. *
  - Urbaitis, Dave
  - Urban, Ernest *
  - Urban, Nathan
  - Uretsky, Barry (Dr.)
  - Urling, George A., Jr. (Dr.) *
  - Urquhart, John (Dr.) *
  - Urschler, Gary
  - Usher, Thomas J.
  - Utley, Frederick B.
  - Utley, Richard
  - Utterback, Everett E. *
- V
  - Vagnucci, Anthony H.
  - Vainchtein, Anna
  - Vaithyanathan, Venugopalan
  - Valdiserri, Ronald
  - Valentich, Frank
  - Valentine, Bryan M.
  - Valesente, Robert
  - Vamosi, Jana
  - Vana, Clara
  - Van Aken, James
  - Vanagas, Elmutis Vladislovas
  - Van Blerkom, Dianna
  - Van Blerkom, Malcolm L.
  - Van Cleve, Susan
  - Vanda, Cynthia
  - Van Dalen, Diebold B.
  - Vandenbossche, Julie
  - Vanderstappen, Harrie
  - Vander Ven, Karen
  - Vandora, Justin
  - Vandora, Thomas
  - Van Dorpe, Jill
  - Van Dorsten, A. C. (Dr.)
  - Van Dusen, Albert (oversize) *
  - Van Epps, Scott
  - Van Houten, Donald
  - Van Kammen, Daniel P. *
  - Van Kirk, L. E. *
  - Van Kirk, Mary Elizabeth *
  - Van Lehn, Kurt
  - Van Mershbergen, Audrey
  - Van Meter, C. T.
  - Vann, Robert L.
  - Vannucci, Albert P.
  - Van Pelt, Alex
  - Vanscoy, Gordon J.
  - Van Scriver, Barbara
  - Van Sickle, C. L. *
  - Van Slyke, Lynette
  - Van Thiel, David H.
  - Van Tillburg, Mark
  - Van Trump, James
  - Van Vuuren, Nancy
  - Vanyukov, Michael
  - Varat, Murray A. *
  - Vargo, Raymond L.
  - Vargus, Brian
  - Varnon, Philip
  - Vasquez, Juan
  - Vasquez, Juan Adolfo
  - Vasvary, John
  - Vaughan, James A. *
  - Vaughan, Maurice H., Jr. (Dr.)
  - Velardo, Frank
  - Veltri, Peter
  - Venberg, Lorraine
  - Venkataramanan, Raman
  - Vensel, Earl W.
  - Venzon, Lindz
  - Verdile, Vincent
  - Verdolini-Marston, Katherine
  - Verfona, Kathleen Dobroseilski
  - Verma, Kamal
  - Vernan, Philip H.
  - Vernick, Judy
  - Very, Frank W. *
  - Veser, Goetz
  - Vester, John W.
  - Vesterlund, Lise
  - Vickroy, Ronald
  - Victor, Jennifer
  - Vidal, Gore
  - Vidic, Radisav
  - Vieh, Walter F. *
  - Vig, Katherine Dryland
  - Vig, Peter S.
  - Vigai, Singh
  - Vilella, Joseph R.
  - Villanueva, Flordeliza
  - Viundt, Wolfgang
  - Vivaro, Filomena
  - Voelker, Paul Henry
  - Vogel, Carol A.
  - Vogel, Harold R (Dr.) & Carol
  - Vogel, Victor
  - Vogt, Molly T.
  - Voinski, John
  - Vollmer, Judith
  - Vollmer, Marian L.
  - Von Appen, Fred
  - Von Bodungen, Max
  - Von der Luft, Robert
  - Von Dirke, Sabine
  - Von Koenigswald, G. H. R. *
  - Von Mering, Otto (Dr.)
  - Voros, Zolton
  - Vorp, David
  - Voss, James F. *
  - Votruba, Martin
  - Vrabie, Mark
  - Vrana, John
  - Vries, Egbert de
  - Vries, John
  - Vujacic, Ivan
  - Vujan, Alexander (Dr.) *
  - Vyas, Anix
- W
  - Wackenhut, Norman A.
  - Wada, Warner
  - Waddell, Susan Sharpe *
  - Wade, Emily
  - Wadhwa, Rajindark *
  - Wadia, Maneck S.
  - Wadsworth, F. L. O. *
  - Wadsworth, Frank W. (Dr.) *
  - Wadsworth, Homer C. *
  - Wadsworth, Marshaman E.
  - Waelder, Robert
  - Waelti, Elizabeth
  - Wagatsuma, Hiroshi
  - Wagman, Nicholas (Dr.) (oversize)
  - Wagner, Alfred C. *
  - Wagner, Amy
  - Wagner, J. Huber *
  - Wagner, Michael
  - Wagner, William
  - Wagnon, Lloyd *
  - Waite, Howard *
  - Waites, Traci
  - Wakefield, Alice L.
  - Wakely, John
  - Wakim, Anthony N.
  - Walbank, Frank W. *
  - Walczak, Witold
  - Wald, Arnold
  - Wald, George *
  - Wald, Niel
  - Waldeck, David
  - Waldheim, Kurt *
  - Walgren, Doug
  - Walker, Amanda
  - Walker, Curtis
  - Walker, Deborah L.
  - Walker, Gilbert
  - Walker, Jawan
  - Walker, Marcedes
  - Walker, Maxine
  - Walker, Ramon
  - Walker, W. K.
  - Walkins, Ralph J.
  - Walkney, Karen
  - Wall, Thomas Burke *
  - Wall, Thomas J. *
  - Wallace, Daniel Henry
  - Wallace, James O.
  - Wallace, John
  - Wallace, Richard C.
  - Wallace, Ruth Taylor (Mrs.) *
  - Wallace, W. E. (Dr.) *
  - Wallace, William D.
  - Wallace, William J. L.
  - Wallach, Alyson
  - Waller, Wilvor C.
  - Wallhauser, Andrew
  - Wallin, J. E. Wallace
  - Wallis, Ramona
  - Wallisch, William J. (Lieutenant Colonel)
  - Walls, Jean Hamilton *
  - Walsh, Arthur C.
  - Walsh, Margaret
  - Walston, F. Ann
  - Walt, Alan Stoy
  - Walter, George Leonard
  - Walter, George R.
  - Walter, George W. (Dr.)
  - Walter, Otis
  - Walter, Paul *
  - Walters, Richard J.
  - Walters, Robert S. (Dr.)
  - Walters, Ron
  - Walthour, Christopher C., Jr.
  - Walton, Clarence C.
  - Walts, Lynn M.
  - Wang, C. F.
  - Wang, Feng
  - Wang, James H. C.
  - Wang, Jian-Zhou
  - Wang, Jijun
  - Wang, Lu-In
  - Wang, Margaret C.
  - Wang, Xiao-Jing
  - Wang, Yi-Tung (Dr.)
  - Wann, Marilyn
  - Wannstedt, Dave
  - Waples, Douglas
  - Warchock, Gary
  - Ward, David F.
  - Ward, Jeremy
  - Ward, Timothy W. *
  - Warden, Katie
  - Wardner, C. Arthur
  - Ware, Carl
  - Ware, James W.
  - Ware, Ralph
  - Warfel, Florence
  - Warford, Reggie
  - Warga, Mary Elizabeth *
  - Warne, Colston E.
  - Warner, Glenn S. "Pop"
  - Warner, Joanne
  - Warner, Jon
  - Warnick, Barbara
  - Warnick, Pat
  - Warnock, Garry F.
  - Warrick, Charles Emery
  - Warriner, Heidi
  - Washabaugh, Robert (Dr.)
  - Washington, Marsha
  - Washington, Nancy
  - Washo, Kevin
  - Wasilewski, Peter
  - Wasserman, Joseph
  - Wasserman, Rhonda
  - Wassie, Tibor
  - Waterhouse, Ellis K.
  - Waterman, Margaret
  - Waterman, Peter M. *
  - Waters, Walter V.
  - Waterson, Albert *
  - Watkins, Gwen
  - Watkins, Jack *
  - Watkins, Ralph J.
  - Waston, Alex
  - Watson, Charles G.
  - Watson, Charles M. *
  - Watson, Dygretta
  - Watson, James Rose
  - Watson, Jesse P. *
  - Watson, Joan E.
  - Watson, Joseph A.
  - Watson, Katherine
  - Watson, Paul *
  - Watson, Richard K.
  - Watson, Robert *
  - Watters, Roy
  - Watts, Phillip
  - Watzke, Beth
  - Way, Abisal John
  - Way, James B., Jr. *
  - Way, Katharine
  - Weaver, G. G.
  - Webb, Alonzo
  - Webb, Kortni
  - Webber, Adam
  - Webber, Steven
  - Weber, C. Edward *
  - Weber, Charles
  - Weber, John *
  - Weber, Lawrence M.
  - Weber, Stephen
  - Weber, Yvonne Roebuck
  - Webner, Franklyn
  - Webster, Ella
  - Webster, Homer J.
  - Webster, Marshall
  - Wechsler, Lawrence
  - Wecht, Cyril
  - Wedekind, Carl *
  - Wedekind, Frank
  - Wedge, Karen
  - Wedel, Janine
  - Weeks, Daniel E.
  - Wei, Evelyn Han-li
  - Weidenhammer, Robert M. *
  - Weidle, Ethan
  - Weidlein, Edward
  - Weidman, John C.
  - Weigle, Arthur (oversize) *
  - Weil, Catherine
  - Weil, G. C.
  - Weil, Maurice H.
  - Weiland, Lisa
  - Weiland, W. F.
  - Weiler, Richard
  - Weinberg, Jason
  - Weinberg, Lee
  - Weinberg, Max H.
  - Weinberg, Roger
  - Weiner, Bluma B.
  - Weiner, Debra K.
  - Weingartner, Rudolph H. *
  - Weinstock, Isadore "Izzy"
  - Weinstraub, Andrew
  - Weintraub, Andrew
  - Weir, Edward
  - Weis, William H.
  - Weiss, David *
  - Weiss, David (oversize) *
  - Weiss, Doyle *
  - Weiss, E. A.
  - Weiss, Harold B.
  - Weiss, Larry
  - Weiss, Martin
  - Weiss, Martin B.
  - Weissbach, Cobi
  - Weissberg, Elaine
  - Weissberger, Barbara
  - Weissfield, Joel
  - Weist, Dale W.
  - Weisz, Donald
  - Weithorn, Lois
  - Welch, George
  - Welch, Gilbert L. *
  - Welch, William
  - Welling, Joel
  - Welling, Phil
  - Wells, Calvin
  - Wells, Everett D. *
  - Wells, Jerome Covell
  - Wells, William *
  - Welsh, Alexander (Dr.)
  - Wen, Agnes
  - Wendell, Richard E.
  - Wendell, Steve
  - Wender, Irving
  - Wendland, Leonard V., PhD
  - Wenger, Kenneth J. *
  - Wenguo, Feng
  - Weniger, Frederick (Dr.)
  - Wenk, Arthur
  - Wentley, Richard
  - Werdman, Anne
  - Werlinch, Joseph
  - Werner, Gerhard *
  - Werner, Harry J.
  - Wernicki, Mike
  - Wertman, Kenneth F. *
  - Wescott, Blaine F. (Dr.)
  - Wescott, Shawn
  - Weslager, C. A.
  - Wesmiller, Susan
  - Wessel, Arthur, Jr.
  - West, Cornel
  - West, Harry H.
  - West, Michael
  - West, Robin
  - Westcott, B. B. *
  - Weston, Lloyd
  - Wetherell, Walter D.
  - Wettick, R. Stanton, Jr.
  - Wettstein, F. O.
  - Wetzel, M. Dan
  - Weyant, Robert
  - Whale, Brandon
  - Whalen, Carol *
  - Whalen, Janey
  - Whalen, Jerome
  - Whatule, Larry J.
  - Wheeler, Harold W.
  - Wheeler, Mark
  - Wheelock, Stefan
  - Whetsell, George W.
  - Whitcomb, David C.
  - White, E. G.
  - White, George
  - White, Guy H.
  - White, Harold Rogers
  - White, Harvey L.
  - White, Janice J.
  - White, Jim
  - White, Nancy
  - White, Patricia Lomando
  - White, Vincent
  - White, Welsh S.
  - White, William Charles
  - White, William L. *
  - Whiteford, William K. *
  - Whitehead, Cortlandt
  - Whitehead, Tony Larry
  - Whitehill, Buell B., Jr.
  - Whiteside, Theresa
  - Whiting, P. W.
  - Whitley, Isadore B.
  - Whitman, Marina *
  - Whitman, Robert F.
  - Whitmer, Carroll A.
  - Whitmer, George
  - Whitmore, Marilyn
  - Whitney, Dorothy K.
  - Whitney, Jacqueline
  - Whitney, Susan L.
  - Whitsel, B. L.
  - Whitten, George
  - Whittier, E. T. *
  - Wholey, C. C.
  - Wholey, Mark
  - Wieand, Harry S.
  - Wichers, Robert
  - Wick, Harriet B.
  - Wicklow, Donald
  - Wideman, John Edgar
  - Wider, Eve
  - Widnell, Christopher C. *
  - Wiebe, Janyce
  - Wiechec, Frank John
  - Wieman, Carl
  - Wiener, Eugene S.
  - Wiesenfeld, Harold
  - Wiggins, Andrew
  - Wight, Byron W.
  - Wightman, John R. *
  - Wikoff, Alan G.
  - Wilburn, Robert C.
  - Wilcox, Craig S.
  - Wilde, Ralph C.
  - Wilds, John
  - Wiley, Clayton
  - Wilhelm, Stephen C.
  - Wilkens, Grover, III (oversize)
  - Wilkes, Paul
  - Wilkins, David
  - Wilkins, Henry
  - Wilkins, Robert H. *
  - Wilkins, William *
  - Wilkinson, Elizabeth Hays
  - Wilkinson, Helen Jean
  - Wilkinson, John
  - Wilks, David, MD *
  - Willard, Charles
  - Willard, Ralph
  - Willem, Michele
  - Willen, Vic *
  - Willenkin, Robert L. *
  - Willey, David
  - Willey, Raymond
  - Williams, Benjamin H.
  - Williams, Brandon
  - Williams, Brian
  - Williams, Carolyn
  - Williams, Edmund
  - Williams, Esther Maud *
  - Williams, George
  - Williams, Gregory Howard
  - Williams, Harold "Josh"
  - Williams, Holly Ann
  - Williams, James *
  - Williams, Jill
  - Williams, John P.
  - Williams, John W.
  - Williams, Mary A.
  - Williams, Max *
  - Williams, Nicole
  - Williams, Philip
  - Williams, Samuel H.
  - Williams, Scott
  - Williams, T. Earl
  - Williams, Thomas DeWitt
  - Williams-Dunn, Lucenia
  - Willis, Richard
  - Willis, William G. *
  - Willoughby, Walter
  - Willus, Michael
  - Wilmer, Richard
  - Wilson, Sir Angus
  - Wilson, August
  - Wilson, Bruce
  - Wilson, Carolynn A. M.
  - Wilson, Gertrude *
  - Wilson, James A. *
  - Wilson, James B.
  - Wilson, John R. *
  - Wilson, Kris
  - Wilson, Mark L.
  - Wilson, Martha (SEE MacDonald, Martha)
  - Wilson, Richard M.
  - Wilson, Robb R.
  - Wilson, Sharon
  - Wilson, Thurlow R. (Dr.)
  - Wilzbach, Margaret
  - Winchell, Sidney W.
  - Windisch, Charles P.
  - Windt, T. H.
  - Windt, Ted
  - Wing, Edward J.
  - Wing, Hugh
  - Wingard, Edgar Ramsey
  - Wingard, Lemuel B. (Dr.)
  - Winkler, Linda
  - Winkler, Norman
  - Winklestein, Alan
  - Winter, Frederick W.
  - Winter, Peter M., MD
  - Winters, Stephen J. *
  - Wintner, Allan (Dr.)
  - Wion, Philip *
  - Wipf, Peter
  - Wischer, George J. (Dr.) *
  - Wise, Albert I. *
  - Wishik, Samuel
  - Wistrand, Erick (Dr.)
  - Witherspoon, Paul A., Jr.
  - Witman, Shepherd L. (Dr.) *
  - Wittenmeyer, Mandy
  - Witthoft, John
  - Wittig, Greg
  - Wittmer, George
  - Witz, Warren R.
  - Wlassics, Tibor
  - Woefel, Susan
  - Woffinden, Neil
  - Wofford, Harris
  - Wohleber, Curt
  - Wolf, E. Alfred
  - Wolf, Gail
  - Wolf, Gerald
  - Wolf, Jacob
  - Wolf, James R. *
  - Wolf, Thomas
  - Wolfarth, Harry W. *
  - Wolfe, Arthur
  - Wolfe, C. Holmes., Jr. *
  - Wolfe, Harvey (Dr.)
  - Wolfe, Richard J.
  - Wolff, Jonathan
  - Wolff, Paul B. (Lieutenant Colonel)
  - Wolford, Jack A.*
  - Wolfson, Evan
  - Wolfson, Sara
  - Wolfson, Sidney
  - Wolke, Robert *
  - Wolken, Jerome J.
  - Wolman, Yecheskel *
  - Wolmark, Norman
  - Woltman, Frederick
  - Womack, Jackie
  - Wong, Y. K. (Dr.) *
  - Woo, Savio
  - Woo, Tse-Chien
  - Wood, Charles L.
  - Wood, Diana
  - Wood, Donna
  - Wood, Geoffrey
  - Wood, Jean *
  - Wood, Mildred L.
  - Wood, Richard D.
  - Wood, Susan
  - Woodcock, Kenneth
  - Wood-Smith, Jane *
  - Woodring, Nancy
  - Woodrow, Castle C.
  - Woodruff, Archibald *
  - Woodruff, John
  - Woods, Barry *
  - Woods, Charles A., Jr. *
  - Woods, Edward A.
  - Woods, George *
  - Woodson, Joanne
  - Woodstra, Sue
  - Woodsworth, Anne
  - Woodward, Jennifer
  - Woodward, Leslie
  - Woolf, Jeanne *
  - Woolridge, Pearl
  - Woolls, Blanche
  - Wooten, Rosemarie
  - Worman, Michael A.
  - Worrell, Derrick
  - Worsey, Michael
  - Worthing, Archie G. (oversize) *
  - Worthington, Leslie B.
  - Worthington, Walter
  - Wosu, Sylvanus N.
  - Wotiz, John Henry
  - Woy, R. Alfred (oversize) *
  - Wrabley, Raymond
  - Wray, Wendell Leonard *
  - Wright, A. B.
  - Wright, George Henrik Von
  - Wright, Jessie
  - Wright, John Ernest
  - Wright, John Joseph Bishop *
  - Wright, Richard
  - Wright, Robert L.
  - Wright, Timothy W.
  - Wright, Verne Colson *
  - Wright, W. H.
  - Writt, William Morgan
  - Wightman, John R.
  - Wu, Andrew
  - Wu, Yumel
  - Wukich, Dane K.
  - Wurdack, John H.
  - Wyckoff, Ralph D.
  - Wycoff, Robert S.
  - Wydra, Michelle
  - Wylie, Douglas W.
  - Wymard, William H. (Dr.)
  - Wynder, Ernst L.
  - Wynn, Richard
  - Wynne, Margaret M.
  - Wynne, Richard
  - Wynnycky, Jason
- X
  - Xiao, Xiao
  - Xie, Wen
  - Xu, Cailu
  - Xu, Yan
- Y
  - Yablonski, Brooke
  - Yablonski, Steven K.
  - Yagi, Yukako
  - Yaich, Lauren
  - Yaillen, Earl R.
  - Yajima, Haruki (Dr.)
  - Yakovlev, Petr
  - Yaksich, Stella
  - Yalowich, Jack
  - Yamatani, Hide *
  - Yanaihora, Nobora (Dr.)
  - Yang, C. K. *
  - Yang, Charlotte W.
  - Yang, Jinlong
  - Yang, Judith C.
  - Yang, Richard
  - Yang, Y. C.
  - Yao, Qingchuan
  - Yarosh, Lisa
  - Yaruss, Jonathon
  - Yahin, Victor
  - Yasko, Joyce M.
  - Yates, Cecil H.
  - Yates, John, Jr. *
  - Yates, Michael
  - Yeager, (Dr.)
  - Yeager, Andrew
  - Yeager, John L.
  - Yeager, William A.
  - Yealy, Donald
  - Yee, Chiang
  - Yee, Robert
  - Yee, W. P. Andrew
  - Yee-ha, Chi
  - Yeh, Joanne
  - Yellin, Samuel
  - Yeskey, Dennis
  - Yildirim, Tuba Pinar
  - Yin, Yong-Quan
  - Ying-Fa, Shih
  - Yinhe, Li
  - Yoakam, Gerald *
  - Yoffe, Jeff
  - Yohman, Debbie
  - Yohn, David S.
  - Yonas, Howard
  - Yong-Zhuo, Chen
  - Yoo, Chung Soo (oversize)
  - Yoo, Seung-Hyun
  - Yookyung, Kim
  - York, Barry
  - York, Andrew Windsor (Duke of)
  - Yoshida, Shiro
  - Yost, George, Jr.
  - Youchak, Richard
  - Young, A. C.
  - Young, A. M. *
  - Young, Alexander
  - Young, Candy
  - Young, Christine L.
  - Young, Earl B., PhD